digitallook.com 2018-08-15

# Web Financial Group • Tech Solutions

### Ownership

In compliance with the provisions of the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council, of April 27 2016, on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (hereinafter referred to as RGPD) we inform you that the personal data provided to the companies pertaining to WEB FINANCIAL GROUP (hereinafter referred to as WFG GROUP) will be included in a database jointly owned by the following companies:

  * WEB FINANCIAL GROUP, S.A., registered in the Mercantile Registry of Madrid Volume 14996, Section 8th, Page 182, Sheet N-250022, VAT Nº: A-82548066, address: Pedro Teixeira 8, 1, 28020 - MADRID (Spain), tel [+34914175350](tel:+34914175350) and email: [info@webfg.com](mailto:info@webfg.com).

### CONTACT

For any matter connected with the processing of data of natural persons by the companies in Web Financial Group you may contact the email address [rgpd@webfg.com](mailto:rgpd@webfg.com), and the telephone number [+34914175350](tel:+34914175350), or else you may also get in touch with our Data Protection Delegate by way of the following email address [DPO@webfg.com](mailto:DPO@webfg.com)

Web Financial Group companies will collect the following information provided by the data subject:

  * **COMMERCIAL CONTACT form:** to deal with and manage the information requests sent by the User with this form.
  *     * **Data collected:** name, phone, email and comments.
    * **Purpose:** to deal with requests for information asked by any means about products and services offered by Web Financial Group, and for the establishment or maintenance of business relationships.
    * **Lawful basis:** based on the consent given by the data subject, Web Financial Group is entitled to process the data provided through the contact request, and in accordance with the legitimate interest in the development and maintenance of business relationships.
    * **Storage limitation::** data will be kept until the moment the data subject requests their cancellation or erasure and once deleted they will be kept for a maximum period of 6 years for the attention and defence of the potential responsibilities arising from the processing.
  * **PROMOTIONAL or NEWSLETTERS:** the submission of information, news, notices, reminders and promotions that may be of your interest, related to the activities of Web Financial Group and its clients.
  *     * **Data collected::** email address, first name and surname. .
    * **Purpose:** the registration of those who are interested in the submission of information, news and promotions, and to establish or maintain business relationships.
    * **Lawful basis:** the provision of data subject's consent to WFG GROUP to be registered in promotional services, and the legitimate interest in the development of business relationships.
    * **Storage limitation:** data will be kept until the moment the data subject requests their cancellation or erasure and once deleted they will be kept for a maximum period of 6 years for the attention and defence of the potential responsibilities arising from the processing.
  * **CURRICULUM OR RECRUITMENT:** to send Curriculum to Web Financial Group via the web or by any other means..
  *     * **Data collected:** professional expertise area, name, surname, telephone, e-mail, CV, cover letter and other personal data related to the Curriculum or professional profile.
    * **Purpose:** management of the application for the recruitment processes published or for other vacancies according to your professional profile that may arise in the future within the activities of Web Financial Group.
    * **Storage limitation:** the data will be kept until you are awarded a job or until you request their erasure. They will therefore be kept for the time necessary for the purpose of the processing, and once concluded they may be kept for a maximum period of 6 years for the attention and defence of the potential responsibilities arising from the processing.
    * **Lawful basis:** consent granted by the candidate.
    * **Recipients:** the data provided and derived from the selection process may be disclosed to:

#####  **Third companies identified by the data subject and that may be necessary for the candidate's request for references.**

  * **SERVICES:** data given for the provision of services by any of the companies pertaining to Web Financial Group. Services will be identified at the time of data collection and registration.
  *     * **Data collected:** first name, ID number, job address, address, email, contact telephone number, and other necessary information depending on the registration requested, and which will be solely necessary for registration in the services offered by Web Financial Group.

In case of registering or logging into your account with the credentials of a social network, we shall have access to part of your information profile in such social networks.

    * **Purpose:** registration of data subjects for the provision of services provided by the WFG GROUP, and to establish and maintain business relationships.
    * **Lawful basis:** the provision of data subject's consent to WFG GROUP to any of the companies pertaining to Web Financial Group for the aforementioned services, and the legitimate interest in the development of business relationships.
    * **Storage limitationn:** the data will be kept for the time necessary for the purpose of the processing or until the moment in which the data subject requests their cancellation or erasure, and once suppressed they may be kept for a maximum period of 6 years for the attention and defence of the potential responsibilities arising from the processing.
    * **Recipients:** Occasionally, your data may be transferred to third parties for the implementation of advertising campaigns that in each case will be previously informed. Reports containing data on users interested in real-time quotes may also be submitted to the Madrid and London Stock Exchanges. Finally, we provide data to social networks such as Facebook and Twitter for campaigns and follower promotions.
  * **Registration and Monitoring of Corporate Social Networks accounts:** personal data that you enable or supply to social networks at the time of becoming a follower of them. The corporate accounts of the social networks of Web Financial Group are the following:
  *     * **TWITTER:** <https://twitter.com/webfg>
    * **LINKEDIN:** <https://www.linkedin.com/company/web-financial-group-s-a->
    * **FACEBOOK:** [](https://www.facebook.com/Bolsamania)
    * **YOUTUBE:** <https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LoMS2fHMn4Y>
    * **FLIPBOARD:** <https://flipboard.com/@Webfg>
  *     * **Data collected::** first name, surname, ID number, address, address, email, telephone number, and other information provided by the corresponding social network.
    * **Purpose:** social network monitoring, and maintenance and development of business relationships.
    * **Lawful basis:** onsent provided by the user to any of the companies pertaining to Web Financial Group, and in accordance with legitimate interest for the development of business relations.
    * **Storage limitation:** data will be kept for as long as it is necessary for the purposes for which they are processed, and then data might be kept during six years at the disposal of Public Administration and Justice Administration in order to determine any liability arising from the processing.
  * **CLIENTS/SUPPLIERS:** professional personal data provided by Clients/Suppliers for the provision of services and management of the legal or contractual relationship.
  *     * **Data collected::** name surnames, ID number, job address, email, job telephone, bank details.
    * **Purpose:** management of service contractual relationship.
    * **Lawful basis:** the existing legal or contractual relationship necessary for the provision of the service..
    * **Storage limitation:** data will be kept for as long as necessary for the purposes for which they are processed, or deletion of same, and once concluded or deleted they might be kept during six years at the disposal of Public Administration and Justice Administration in order to determine any liability arising from the processing.
  * The Interested Party knows and expressly agrees that the acceptance of any of the afore-mentioned purposes entails the inclusion of his/her data in the common Databases of the companies belonging to Web Financia Group, and the assignment of his/her data of a personal nature to the companies that are specified at all times at website www.webfinancialgroup.com, with the possibility that they may be used by all of them for the afore-mentioned purposes. Such assignment takes place with the same processing purposes, same data categories, same storage time, and similar exercise of rights. You may oppose at any time such assignment or any of those mentioned in the previous sections by way of postal mail to the address Pedro Teixeira 8, 1, 28020 – Madrid - Spain or by email to the address [rgpd@webfg.com](mailto:rgpd@webfg.com). 

Apart from the afore-mentioned assignments, the disclosure of data to third parties is not envisaged, except for the provision of third-party services by data processors with which Web Financial Group has signed the corresponding data processing agreements and has verified that they provide sufficient guarantees to implement proper technical and organizational measures that meet the requirements of the GDPR, assuring the protection of data subjects’ rights. 

### EXERCISE OF RIGHTS

The User has recognized his/her rights of access, rectification or erasure, restriction, objection and portability of his/her data controlled by WFG. As long as the reason for processing continues to exist or his/her personal data are not deleted from our files, we shall go on processing his/her data as they are necessary for the processing and he/she remains interested in forming part of them. The Interested Party may exercise his/her rights at any time by means of sending a postal communication to WFG at the address stated above or by email to the address [rgpd@webfg.com](mailto:rgpd@webfg.com), attaching a document that substantiates his/her identity and expressly specifying the right that he/she wishes to exercise.

Similarly, the Interested Party has his/her rights recognized to access, rectification, suppression, limitation, opposition and portability of his/her data under the responsibility of the companies in Web Financial Group. The Interested Party may exercise his/her rights at any time by means of sending a postal communication to WFG at the address stated above or by email to the addres [rgpd@webfg.com](mailto:rgpd@webfg.com), attaching a document that substantiates his/her identity and expressly specifying the right that he/she wishes to exercise.

The data subject has the right to withdraw his or her consent for the processing by Web Financial Group. He/she also has the right to lodge a complaint stemming from the processing of his/her personal data before the Spanish Data Protection Agency (http://www.agpd.es).

Likewise, the User shall have the right to withdraw his or her consent for the processing by WFG GROUP. He/she also has the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. 

### TECHNICAL AND ORGANIZATIONAL SECURITY MEASURES

Web Financial Group has adopted the necessary technical and organisational measures to guarantee the safety and integrity of data, and to protect them from any alteration, loss, processing or unauthorized access.

### DATA PROVIDED

Data collected from the forms on this Website are those strictly necessary to meet your request, which you voluntarily communicate to us. The refusal to provide data marked as mandatory shall impede the provision of the services requested. In order to keep your personal data updated, you should inform us of any change that may take place in relation to them, otherwise we shall not be answerable for their accuracy. Likewise, in those cases where third party data are disclosed the data subject undertakes to inform them about the content of this privacy policy.

The Interested Party undertakes to forward as soon as possible to Web Financial Group any change and correction of his/her data of a personal nature so that the information contained in the Web Financial Group Activity Records remains updated at all times.

By virtue of the legitimate interest of companies pertaining to Web Financial Group the data subject´s personal data may be used for the establishment or maintenance of business relations by any means, including electronically, so as to inform him/her regarding products and services offered by these, with the option open at any time of opposing such processing for business purposes by means of remitting a postal communication to the address Pedro Teixeira 8, planta 1, 28020 – Madrid - Spain, or via email to the address [rgpd@webfg.com](mailto:rgpd@webfg.com).
